Guide to the Joseph Stewart Fruton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Joseph Stewart Fruton papers
1900-2007
MS 1396
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
39.25
The papers include correspondence and laboratory notebooks documenting Joseph Stewart Fruton's career as a professor of biochemistry and the history of medicine.
Fruton, Joseph S. (Joseph Stewart), 1912-2007
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Joseph Stewart Fruton, 1994 and 2002.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Biographical / Historical
Joseph Stewart Fruton was born in 1912. He received a BA from Columbia University in 1931 and earned his Ph.D. from there in 1934. Fruton served on the staff of the Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research for ten years, before coming to Yale University in 1945. In 1950 Fruton was promoted to the rank of full professor and in 1957 was named the Eugene S. Higgins Professor of Biochemistry. He was named professor emeritus in 1982. Fruton died on July 29, 2007, in New Haven, Connecticut.
A leading scientist in the field of the biochemistry of proteins, Fruton is also a scholar of the history of medicine. His published works include General Biochemistry, Molecules and Life, A Skeptical Biochemist, A Bio-bibliography for the History of the Biomedical Sciences since 1800, and Selected Bibliography of Biographical Data for the History of Biochemistry since 1800.
Scope and Contents
The papers include correspondence, lectures, writings, photographs, and laboratory notebooks documenting Joseph Stewart Fruton's career as a professor of biochemistry and the history of medicine. Family photographs are also included in the papers.
FRUTON CORRESPONDENTS
Aaboe, Asger
Aaviksaar, Aavo
Andreeva, Natalya S.
Abernethy, John L.
Abir-Am. Pnina G.
Abler, Charles.
Aboderin, Akintola
Abramson, Harold A.
Accounts of Chemical Research
Acher, Roger
Acheson, Dean
Adams, Elijah
Adams, Roger
Adolph, Edward F.
Adrian, Richard H.
Aimoto, Saburo
Akabori, Shiro
Akhtar, M
Alexander, Nicholas M.
Allen, Garland E.
Altman, Sidney
Ambler, Richard
American Cyanamid Company
American Peptide Society
American Philosophical Society
American Scientist
Anderson, Beverly S.
Anderson, Ervin O.
Anderson, George W.
Anderson, Rudolph J.
Anfinsen, Christian B.
Anslow, W. Parker
Antonov, Viktor K.
Aoyagi, Tataaki
Applebury, Meredithe
Arigoni, Duilio
Armstrong, Wallace D.
Arndt, Donna J.
Arnow, L. Earle
Ash, Adrienne
Ashby, Eric
Augustinsson, Klas-Bertil
Auld, Gavid
Babb, James T.
Bach, Stefan J.
Bacon, J.S.D.
Bade, Maria L.
Bailey, J. Leggett
Bailey, Kenneth
Baldwin, Ernest
Ball, Eric G.
Balls, Arnold Kent
Ballou, Clinton E.
Bally, Peter
Barnabas, John
Barnum, Cyrus P.
Barrett, Alan J.
Barron, Bruce A.
Barron, Donald H.
Barron, E.S. Guzman
Bartels, Ditta
Bartlett, Paul D.
Barzun, Jacques
Bates, Harold M.
Battersby, Alan
Bauer, Carl Axel
Baumer, Franklin L.
Bayer, Ernst
Beach, Eliot F.
Beadle, George W.
Beams, Jesse W.
Beard, Howard H.
Bearn, Alexander G.
Bechtel, William
Beeson, Paul B.
Behre, Charles H.
Behrens, Otto K.
Bellhorn, Margaret B.
Bender, Myron L.
Bendich. Aaron
Benesch, Reinuold
Benfey, Bruno G.
Benfey, Theodor
Benison, Saul
Benkovic, Stephen J.
Benner, Steven A.
Benoiton, N. Leo
Bentley, Ronald
Benzer, Seymour
Berenblum, Isaac
Berg, Paul
Berger, Rainer
Bergmann, Max
Bergmann, Werner
Bergström, Sune
Berliner, Robert W.
Beyermas, Hugo C.
Bickel, Marcel H.
Bigwood, Edouard J.
Bing, Frankiln C.
Binkley, Francis
Biochemistry
Bishop, Jonathan S.
Black, Simon
Blass, Judith
Blobel, Günter
Bloch, Konrad E.
Block, Richard J.
Blout, Elkan R.
Blum, Jacob Joseph
Bockelman, Charles K.
Bodansky, Oscar
Bodanszky, Muklos
Boedefeld, Edith
Boell, Edgar J.
Boissonas, Roger
Bondy, Philip K.
Bonner, David M.
Bonner, James
Bonnichsen, Roger
Booth, Christopher
Bornstein, Paul
Borsook, Henry
Bovarnick, Max
Boyde, T.R.C.
Boyer, Paul D.
Bozler, Hermann
Bradley, Harold
Brainard, William C.
Branch, Irving L.
Brand, Erwin
Brandt, Ira
Braunstein, Aleksandr E.
Brenner, Max
Breslow, Ronald
Brewster, Kingman
Bricas, Evanghelos
Brieger, Gert H.
Briggs, Martha S.
Bright, Mabel H.
Brill, Arthur S.
Brink, Norman G.
Briscoe, Anne M.
Brobeck, John R.
Brock, Thomas D.
Brock, William H.
Brocklehurst, Keith
Bromley, D. Allan
Bronk, Detlev W.
Bronowski, Jacob
Brooks, Chandler McC.
Brown, Barbara I.
Brown, George B.
Brown, Ruby V.
Brownstein, Allen
Bruce-Chwatt, Leonard J.
Bruckner, Viktor
Bruice, Thomas C.
Buchanan, Donald L.
Buchanan, John M.
Buck, Norman S.
Bücher, Theodor
Büttner, Johannes
Bull, Henry J.
Bumpus, Merlin F.
Bunting, Henry
Burdick, C. Lalor
Burford, M G
Burgen, Arnold
Burn, Harold
Burrow, Gerard N.
Burton, Kenneth
Busch, Harris
Butterfield, Herbert
Calabresi, Quido
Calvin, Melvin
Cammarata, Peter S.
Campbell, Peter N.
Canellakis, Evangelo S.
Cannan, R. Keith
Cannon, Walter B.
Cappelletti, Vincenzo
Carlson, Warren A.
Carnahan, James E.
Carpenter, Frederick H.
Carpenter, Samuel C.
Carsten, Mary E.
Carter, Charles E.
Carter, Herbert E.
Casnellie, John
Cassidy, Harold G.
Cattell, Jaques
Chain, Ernst B.
Chambers, Robert
Chance, Britton
Chantrenne, Hubert
Chargaff, Erwin
Chase, Aurin M.
Chibnall, Albert Charles
Christensen, Einar
Ciba Foundation
Cirillo, Vincent P.
Claesson, Stig
Clapp, Leallyn B.
Clark, Malcolm V.
Clark, William M.
Clark-Lewis, John W.
Clark-Walker, G D
Clarke, Edwin
Clarke, Hans T.
Clement, David
Clement, Gerald K.
Cohen, Barnett
Cohen, Georges N.
Cohen, I. Bernard
Cohen, Jeffrey L.
Cohen, Louis A.
Cohen, Philip P.
Cohen, Saul G.
Cohen, Seymour S.
Cohn, Edwin J.
Cohn, Mildred
Cohn, Waldo E.
Colas, Antonio
Cold Spring Harbor Symposia
Cole, William H.
Coleman, Joseph E.
Coleman, William
Coles, James S.
Collier, H. Bruce
Colowick, Sidney
Columbia Broadcasting System
Columbia Universoty
Common Knowledge
Commonwealth Fund
Compton, Jack
Conant, James B.
Connor, Ralph
Consolazio, William V.
Contemporary Anthors
Cook, Daniel C.
Coon, Minor J.
Cooper, James W.
Cooper, William
Cope, Arthur C.
Cordes, Eugene H.
Corey, Elias J.
Corey, Robert B.
Cori, Carl F. & Gerty T.
Cornatzer, W. Eugene
Corner, George W.
Cornish-Bowden, Athel J.
Coryell, Charles D.
Costello, Charles D.
Cournand, Andre
Courtois, Jean Emile
Cowgill, George R.
Cox, Herald R.
Craddock, Valda M.
Craig, Gordon A.
Craig, Lyman C.
Cranefield, Paul F.
Crawford, Bryce
Crawford, Elisabeth
Crescetelli, Frederick
Crewther, W G
Crick, Francis H.C.
Crombie, Alistair C.
Cronan, John E.
Croxatto, Hector R.
Cullman, W. Arthur
Cunningham, Bruce A.
Cunningham, Lew S.
Cupovic, Ilinka S.
Cushley, Robert J.
Dagley, Stanley
Dakin, Henry D.
Dalgleish, Charles E.
Dannenberg, Arthur M.
Danowski, Theodore S.
Darby, William J.
Darling, George B.
Davenport, Horace W.
Davidson, James Norman
Davie, Earl W.
Davies, David R.
Davis, Bernard D.
Davis, Stanley H.
Dawson, Charles R.
Debye, Peter
DeDuve, Christian
Dekker, Charles A.
De La Haba, Gabriel
Delaney, Robert
Delbrück, Max
Delenick, Joann C.
Delpierre, Georges R.
DeMore, Dorian
Denkwalter, Robert G.
Dent, Charles
Desnuelle, Pierre
Determann, \helmut
Deuchar, Elizabeth
Deuel, Harry J.
Dexter Award
Dickens, Frank
Dickman, Sherman R.
Dictionary of American Biography
Dictionary of Scientific Biogr.
DiMaio, Daniel
Dintzis, Howard M.
Dissenters Club
Ditter, James E.
Dixon, Henry B.F.
Dobson, Geoffrey P.
Doerr, Juergen
Doherty, David G.
Doisy, Edward A.
Donner, Jacob
Donohue, Jerry
Donzelot, Pierre
Doscher, Marilynn S.
Doudoroff, Michael
Dowben, Robert M
Dowmont, Yadviga P.
Doyle, William L.
Drabkin, David L.
Drenth, Jan
Drey, Charles N.C.
Driscoll, P. Elizabeth
Dubos, René J.
Dudac, Pamela
Dunn, Leslie C.
Dunn, Max S.
Durell, Jack
DuVigneuad, Vincent
Dwyer, Hugh L.
Eagle, Harry
Eagleston, William P.
Ebbert, Arthur
Ebert, Robert H.
Edelstein, Stuart
Edelman, Gerald M.
Edman, Pehr
Edsall, John T.
Egami, Fujio
(Paul) Ehrlich Prize
Einstein, Albert
Eklund, Jon
Elderfield, Robert C.
Elema, Bene
Eliot's Books
Elliott, Elizabeth J.
Elliott, Stuart D.
Ellis, Drummond
Ellis, Stanley
Elvehjem, Conrad A.
Emerson, Kendall
Emery, Thomas F.
Encyclopedia Americana
Engel, Lewis L.
Engelhardt, Vladimir A.
Engelman, Donald M.
Epstein, Franklin E.
Erdman, Albert J.
Erlanger, Bernard F.
Ernst-Fonberg, Mary Lou
Erwin, Robert
Essex College of Medicine
Evans, Earl A.
Evans, Lester J.
Fahrney, David
Fairclough, Gordon F.
Falmagne, Paul
Fanger, Michael W.
Fantini, Bernardino
Farrel, Franklin
Farthing, Jihn
Feder, Aaron
Feigl, Fritz
Fenn, Wallace O.
Fenton, Paul F.
Ferguson, John B.
Fersht, Alan R.
Fetter, Jean
Fieser, Louis F.
Fine, Morris S.
Finkelstein, Alan I.
Finkenstaedt, John T.
Finn, Frances M.
Finlay, Alexander C.
Fischer, Albert
Fischer, Edmond H.
Fischer, Hermann O.L.
Fisher, Reginald B.
Flavin, Martin
Fleckenstein, Karen
Florkin, Marcel
Fodor, Paul
Fogg, Gordon Elliott
Folkers, Karl A.
Foltmann, Bent
Foote, Franklin M.
Fortunato, Louis R.
Fox, Robert L.
Fox, Ronald
Fox, Sidnay W.
Foyle, Christina
Frankenfield, Alan W.
Fraenkel-Conrat, Heinz
Frantz, Ivan D.
Frauenfelder, Hans
Fredericksen, James M.
Freedman, Louis
W.S. Freeman and Co.
Freimer, Carl A.
French, A. James
Fried, Josef
Fried, Melvin
Friedman, Herbert C.
Frigerio, Norman F.
Fromageot, Claude
Fruton, Charles and Ella
Fruton, Joseph S.
Fujii, Setsuro
Fulton, John F.
Furniss, Edgar S.
Gaebler, Oliver Henry
Gale, Ernest F.
Galston, Arthur W.
Gardner, John W.
Garner, Wendell R.
Garnier, Jean
Garrido Malo, Marco A.
Garwin, Jeffery L.
Gasser, Herbert S.
Gates, Marshall
Geiger, Rolf
Geison, Gerald L.
Gelb, Michael H.
George, Philip
Georgi, Ann B.
Gest, Howard
Ghosh, Jagid J.
Giamatti, A, Bartlett
Gilder, Helena
Giles, Norman H.
Gillispie, Charles C.
Gilman, Henry
Ginodman, Lev M.
Glas, Eduard
Glass, Bentley
Glaudemans, Cornelis P.J.
Glaus, Beat
Goddard, David R.
Goheen, Robert F.
Goldberg, Michael I.
Goldman, Peter
Goldsmith, Timothy H.
Goldstein, Abraham S.
Goldstein, Allan L.
Goldstein, Avram
Goldstine, Herman H.
Golumbic, Calvin
Gonzalez, Elsa L.
Goodman, DeWitt S.
Goodman, Irving
Goodman, Louis S.
Goodman, Murray
Goodman, Roy E.
Gordillo, Guido L.
Gormsen, Harald
Gorska, Edith
Gortner, Ross A., Jr.
Gosalvez y Gosalvez, Mario
Gottschalk, Alfred
Goudsmit, Samuel
Grachis, Dimitri
Graduate Journal
Graff, Samuel
Granick, Sam
Granit, Rgnar
Grant, Cynthia T.
Grantham, Jean
Gratzer, Walter
Graubard, Mark
Gray, George W.
Gray, Hanna H.
Gray, Philip P.
Green, Arda Alden
Green, David E.
Greenbaum, Lowell M.
Greene, John C.
Greengard, Paul
Greenstein, Jesse P.
Greenwald, Isidor
Gressley, Gene M.
Grimshaw, William
Grinstein, Louise S.
Grisolia, Santiago
Griswold, A. Whitney
Grmek, Mirko D.
Grobovsky, Laura V.
Gross, Erhard
Gross, Erwin George
Gruber, Max
Grummitt, Oliver
Grundfest, Harry
Guerlac, Henry
Geggenheim Foundation
Guillemin, Roger
Gunsalus, Irwin C.
Gurin, Samuel
Gutfreund, Herbert
Gutmann, Helmut R.
Gutowsky, Herbert S.
Gutte, Bernd
Haas, Paul
Haddow, Alexander
Hadjivassiliou, Anthony
Hafner, Klaus
Hahn, Roger
Hall, Diana Long
Hall, Ross H.
Hall, V.M.D.
Hamilton, Gordon A.
Hamilton, Paul H.
Hammett, Louis P.
Handler, Philip
Hanes, Charles S.
Hankinson, E. Leroy
Hanson, Horst
Hanson, Kenneth R.
Harbeson, John
Harbury, Henry A.
Hardman, Michael J.
Harington, Charles R.
Harrington, William F.
Harris, J. Ieuan
Harris, Roger
Harrison, John A.
Harrower, Norman
Harte, Robert A.
Hartley, Brian S.
Hartree, Edawrd F.
Harvard University
Harvey, A. McGehee
Harvey, E. Newton
Harvey Society
Haskins, Caryl P.
Hass, George M.
Hassan, Mohammed H.A.
Hassialis, Menelaos D.
Hassid, William Zev
Hastings, A, Baird
Haugaard, Gotfred
Haurowitz, Felix
Heald, Peter J.
Hearn, Walter R.
Hecht, Selig
Heilbron, Ian
Heimbrook, David C.
Hein, George E,
Heinemann, Martin
Heinrich, C. Peter
Heller, Josef
Henderson, James
Henderson, Lawrence J.
Henes, Jill B.
Heppel, Leon A.
Herbst, Robert M.
Herriott, Roger M.
Hershenson, Susan
Hershey, Alfred D.
Hershey Conference
Hess, George P.
Hesse, F.
Hettinger, Thomas P.
Hiatt, Howard H.
Hickel, Erika
Hiebert, Erwin N.
Hill, Archibald V.
Hill, Arthur J.
Hill, Julian W.
Hill, Robert L.
Hiltunen, Terry E.
Hinoe, Albert
Himsworth, Harold P.
Hink, Rupert
Hird, Frank J.R.
Hirohata, Ryozo
Hirs, Werner C.H.
Hirsch, James G.
Hirschmann, Hans
Hirschmann, Ralph F.
Historical Records of Australian Science
History and Philosophy of the Life Sciences
History of Science Society
Hitchings, George H.
Hitchcock, David I.
Hixsn, Susan H.
Hoagland, Mahlon B.
Hoberman, Henry D.
Hodgkin, Dorothy M.C.
Hoffman, Joseph F.
Hoffmann, Roald
Hoffmann-Ostenhof, Otto
Hofmann, Klaus H.
Hofmann, Theo
Hofstee, Barend H.J.
Hogan, Albert E.
Hogness, David S.
Holden, Reuben A.
Hollaender, Alexander
Hollands, T. Ralph
Holley, Robert W.
Hollond, Henry A.
Holloway, Michael R.
Holman, Halsted R.
Holmes, Frederic L.
Holter, Heinz
Hoobler, Icie Macy
Hope, Derek B.
Hopkins, F. Gowland
Horecker, Bernard L.
Hornicek, Anton
Hornig, Donald F.
Horsfall, Frank L.
Horvath, Csaba
Hotchkiss, Rollin D.
Howard-Flanders, Howard
Howe, Eugene E.
Howland, John
Hruby, Victor J.
Hubbard, Ruth
Huggins, Charles
Hughes, Vernon W.
Hummel, John P.
Humphreys, Robert E.
Hunt, Carlton C.
Huntington Library
Hurd, Charles D.
Hurwitz, Jerard
Husain, Syed S.
Hutchinson, G. Evelyn
Ihde, Aaron J.
Inagami, Tadashi
Ing, H. Raymond
Ingle, Dwight J.
Ingram, Vernon M.
Inouye, Ken
International Congress of Biochemistry 1964
International Journal of Peptide and Protein Chemistry
International Union of Biochem.
Interscience Publishers
Iodice, Arthur A.
Iowa State Universiity
Irving, George W.
ISIS
Ito, Akira
Izumiya, Nobuo
Jackson, Kirby E.
Jackson, Richard W.
Jackson, Stanley W.
Jacobs, Walter A.
Jacobsen, Cecil
Jacoby, Steven
Jakoby, William B.
Jakubke, Hans-Dieter
James, Frank
James, Laylin K.
James, Michael N.G.
Jandorf, Bernard J.
Janko, Jan
Jencks, William P.
Johanssen, Jack T.
Johnson, Alan W.
Johnson, Marvin J.
Johnson, Patricia R.
Johnston, Michael A.
Johnston, Robert B.
Johsnton, Waldo C.M.
Jolles, Pierre
Jones, Donald F.
Jones, Ewart R.H.
Jones, J.H.
Jones, Mary Ellen
Jones, Paul R.
Jorpes, Erik
Joslin, Elliott P.
Journal of the American Chemical Society
Journal of Biological Chemistry
Journal of the History of Medicine
Journal of Organic Chemistry
Judson, Horace F.
Jung, Michel
Kabaservice, Geoffrey M.
Kabat, Elvin A.
Kac, Mark
Kägi, Jeremias
Kaiser, Emil Thomas
Kalckar, Herman M.
Kalf, George F.
Kalnitsky, George
Kamber, B.
Kamen, Martin D.
Kantrowitz, Rosalkind J.
Kaplan, Phillip
Karison, Peter
Kassell, Beatrice
Katchalski, Ephraim
Katsoyannis, Panayotis G.
Katunuma, Nobuhiko
Katz, Alan
Kauer, James C.
Kauffman, George A.
Kay, Lily E.
Keil, Brivoj
Keilin, David
Keller, Elizabeth R.
Kemp, Daniel S.
Kendrew, John C.
Kennedy, Eugene P.
Kern, Milton
Kernbauer, Alois
Kerr, Chester B.
Kerr, Edith
Khorana, H. Gobind
Kigg, John G.
Kies, Marian W.
Kilgore, Harley M.
Kilgour, Frederick G.
Kind, C. Albert
King, Charles G.
King, Earl J.
King, Frederick E.
King, Te Piao
Kirby, Anthony J.
Kirkwood, John G.
Kirkwood, Platonia
Kirsch, Jack F.
Kirschenbaum, Donald M.
Kissick, William L.
KLatskin, Gerald
Klee, Werner A.
Klein, Martin J.
Kleiner, Israel
Kleinkauf, Klaus
Kligerman, Morton M.
Kline, C. Mahlon
Kline, Daniel L.
Klyne, William
Knappenberger, Margaret H.
Knight, Martha
Knobil, Ernst
Knowles, Jeremy R.
Knox, W. Eugene
Kodama, Keizo
Koepfli, Joseph B.
Körner, Stephan
Kohler, Robert E.
Konigsberg, William H.
Konopka, Stanislaw
Kornberg, Arthur
Kornberg, Hans L.
Korner, Asher
Koshland, Daniel E.
Kostka, Vladimir
Kotitschke, Ronald
Kottler, Dorian B.
Kotyk, Arnost
Krampitz, Lester O.
Krebs, Hans A.
Krehl, Willard A.
Krenitsky, Thomas A.
Krisch, Klaus
Kroll, Harry
Kuhn, Thomas S.
Kuki, Atsuo
Kullmann, Willi
Kunitz, Moses
Kurahashi, Kiyoshi
Kusch, Polykarp
Kushlan, Samuel D.
Labis, Sophia
Lalor Foundation
Lande, Saul
LaNoue, Kathrn F.
Lapp, Claude J.
Lardy, Henry A.
Larner, Joseph
Laskowski, Michael
Laskowski, Michael, Jr.
Lauffer, Max A.
Lavin, George I.
Lawyer, Arthir L.
Leake, Chauncey D.
Lederberg, Joshua
Lederer, Edgar
Legg, Grant D.
Lehman, I. Robert
Lehmann, Fritz Erich
Lehninger, Albert L..
Leicester, Hnery M.
Lennox, Edwin S.
Lerner, Aaron B.
Letocha, Charles
Levin, Louis
Levine, Elliot M.
Levitt, Monte
Levy, Anthony L.
Levy, Harry A.
Levy, Milton
Lewis, Howard B.
Li, Chao Hao
Library of Congress
Lichtenstein, Noah
Liebecq, Claude
Liebert, Herman W.
Liebow, Averill A.
Lienhard, Gustav E.
Lifton, Robert J.
Light, Albert J.
Lilly Award
Lilly Research Laboratories
Lin, Tsau Yen
Lincoln, Asa L.
Lindbeck, Anne
Lindenmann, Jean
Linderstrom-Lang, Kaj
Lindskog, Gustaf E.
Link, Karl Paul
Linville, Robert G.
Lipmann, Fritz
Lippard, Vernon M.
Lipscomb, William
Litwack, Gerald
Liu, Darrell H.
Lloyd, David P.C.
Loach, Paul A.
Lockwood, Sally F.
Loeb, Lawrence A.
Loeb, Robert F.
Loewi, Otto
Loftfield, Robert B.
Long, C.N. Hugh
Longcope, Warfield T.
Lotspeich, William D.
Louria, Jean S.
Lovett, Sidney
Low, Barbara W.
Lowbridge, John
Lowe, Gordon
Lowry, Oliver H.
Luck, J. Murray
Luisi, P.L.
Lukens, Lewis N.
Lumry, Rufus
Lundbaek, Knud
Luria, Salvador E.
Lustig, Irene
Lwoff, Andre
Lynen, Feodor
Lynn, Hilda B.
McCarty, Maclyn
McClintic Foundation
McCune, Michael
MacDonald, Carol
MacDonald, Herbert J.
McDonald, J. Ken
McElroy, William D.
McGuire, William J.
McGrady, Patrick
McGraw-Hill Book Co.
MacInnes, Duncan A.
Nackenzie, Cosmo G.
McKhann, Guy
McKinley, James L.
McKinley-McKee, John S.
McKusick, Victor A.
MacLane, Saunders
McLaughlin, George D.
McLean, John R.
MacLeod, Colin M.
McMahon, Brian
McManus, I. Rosabelle
McMenany, Rapier Hayden
McNeil, Douglas O.
Maaloe, Ole U.
Maas, Werner K.
Macklis, Roger
Macy Foundation
Maddox, J. Kenneth
Magasanik, Boris
Makinen, Marvin W.
Malmström, Bo G.
Mancini, Joseph A.
Mandelstam, Joel
Mandelstam, Paul
Mandl, Ines
Mangel, Walter F.
Mann, Thaddeus
Manning, James M.
Marchesi, Vincent T.
Mardashev, Sergei
Margenau, Henry
Margoliash, Emanuel
Markham, Roy
Markert, Clement L.
Marks, Paul A.
Markus, Richard L.
Markussen, Jan
Marrian, Denis H.
Marshall, Victor F.
Martin, Archer J.P.
Martin, Constance R.
Maruyama, Koscar
Mason, Howard S.
Masur, Jack
Mathieu, Marcel
Matthew, Margaret
Matthews, Brian W.
Matthews, David M.
Mattill, Henry A.
Mattis, Jeffrey A.
Maull, Nancy
Mautner, Henry G.
Maxwell, Richard E.
Mayer, Jean
Maynard, Leonard A.
Mayr, Ernst
Mazana, Javier
Mazumdar, Pauline
Mead, James F.
Meader, Ralph G.
Meagher, Richard B.
Medizhradszky, Kalman
Mehler, Alan H.
Meienhofer, Johannes
Meinhart, Josephine O.
Meinsen, Kurt
Meister, Alton
Mellanby, Edward
Mendelsohn, Everett
Merrifield, R. Bruce
Merriman, Daniel
Merton, Robert K.
Metcalf, Keyes D.
Metrione, Robert M.
Metzdorf, Robert F.
Meyer, Kurt H.
Meyer, William L.
Meyerhof, Otto
Miles, Otokar
Miles, Wyndham D.
Miller, John Perry
Miller, Leon L.
Miller, Perry L.
Miller, Spencer F.
Milligan, W. Oliver
Minakami, Shigeki
Mintz, Beatrice
Mirsky, Alfred E.
Mirsky, Sonya
Moberg, Caro L.
Moe, Henry A.
Möhle, Walter
Möller, K. Max
Moldave, Kivie
Molitor, Bernadette
Mondale, Walter F.
Monod, Jacques
Moore, Stanford
Moorehouse, Terrill S.
Morawetz, Herbert
Morgan, Graham
Morgan, Neil
Morihara, Kazayuki
Morison, Robert S.
Morris, Colin J.O.R.
Morrison, Bruce A.
Morrison, Martin
Morton, Richard A.
Mosini, Valeria
Mudd, S. Harvey
Mueller, J. Howard
Muller, Hermann J.
Multhauf, Robert P.
Munro, Hamish N.
Munson, Paul L.
Murao, Sawao
Murphy, Alexander J.
Murray, A. Rosemary
Myant Ruth
Mycek, Mary J.
Myer, Yash P.
Nadel, Ida K.
Nagamatsu, Atsuo
Nagel, Ernest
Nagy, Stephen M.
Najjar, Victor A.
Nakamura, Shojiro
Narain, Ram
Nash. Irwin
National Academy of Sciences
National Endowment for the Humanities
National Science Fair
National Science Foundation
Nature
Needham, Dorothy M.
Needham, Joseph
Negus, Sidney S.
Nelbach, Jean
Nesvadba, Hans
Neubauer, Alfred
Neuberg, Carl
Neuberger, Albert
Neugebauer, Gerry
Neugebauer, Otto
Neves, Armando G.
New England Enzyme Center
Newman, Albert B.
Newman, Melvin S.
Newth, Frederick H.
Nicholas, John S.
Nicholls, Robert V.
Nicole-Genty, Genevieve
Niebyl, Peter H.
Nieinann, Carl G.
Nier, Alfred O.C.
Nilsson, Karen
Nishikawa, Alfred H.
Nitschmann, Hans
Nobel Foundation
Nobel Symposium
Noda, Lafayette
Noltmann, Ernst A.
Noonan, Julia A.
Nord, Friedrich F.
Nordwig, Arnold
Norris, Earl R.
Norris, Howard E.
Northrop, John H.
Novelli, G. David
Novikoff, Alex B.
Nowinski, Wiktor W.
Nugey, A.S.
Nuland, Sherwin B.
Numbers, Ronald, L.
Nungester, Walter J.
Nye, Mary Jo
Oakes, John B.
Ochoa, Severo
Ockerse, Albert B.
Ogata, Hatanori
Ogle, James D.
Ogston, Alexander G.
O'Hearn, Charles M.
Ohnishi, Masatake
Okuda, Yoshihiro
Olby, Robert C.
Olitsky, Peter K.
Olitzki, A.L.
Olley, June N.
Ollis, William D.
Olofson, Roy A.
Olsen, Aksel G.
Oncley, J. Lawrence
Ong, David E.
Oppenheimer, Bernard
Oppenheimer, Jane M.
Oppido, Kathryn A.
Orekhovich, Vasili N.
Ornston, L. Nicholas
Oser, Bernard L.
Osserman, Elliott F.
Otteson, Martin
Ourisson, Guy
Ovchinnikov, Yuri A.
Packard, Charles
Packer, Lester
Page, Irvine H.
Palade, George E.
Pappenheimer, John R.
Parascandola, John
Pardee, Arthur B.
Parnas, Jacob K.
Partridge, Stanley Miles
Patton, Alva Rae
Paul, Harry W.
Paul, Karl Gustav
Pauling, Linus
Pavaranam, S.K.
Pelikan, Jaroslav
Penefsky, Harvey S.
Perham, Richard
Perkins, Henrietta T.
Pen, Edward R.
Perlmann, Gertrude
Person, Harlow S.
Perutz, Max F.
Petermann, Mary
Peters, John P.
Peters, Rudolph A.
Peterson, Andrew J.
Peterson, William H.
Pevarada, Philip T.
Peyer, Urs
Peyre, Henri
Pfeiffer, John
Pfleiderer, Gerhard
Phelps, Reginald H.
Phillips, David C.
Phillips, D.M.
Phillips, Robert A.
Piel, Gerard
Pierce, John G.
Pierson, George W.
Pine, Norman W.
Polakoski, Kenneth L.
Polan, Mary Lake
Polanyi, Michael
Poliakoff, Hania
Pollard, Ernest C.
Pollock, Martin R.
Pontremoli, Sandro
Popjak, George
Porter, Rodney R.
Potter, Van R.
Pottle, Frederick A.
Poulson, Donald F.
Poynter, F. Noel L.
Prelog, Vladimir
Prescott, John A.
Price, Charles C.
Price, David E.
Price, Derek deS.
Putnam, Frank W.
Quarterly Review of Biology
Quastel, Juda H.
Quine, Willard V.
Quiocho, Florante
Rabi, I.I.
Racadot, Jean
Racker, Efraim
Radzinowicz, Leon
Raju, Esukapalli V.
Rakitzis, Emmanuel T.
Ramachandran, Gopalasamudram N.
Rapaport, Samuel M.
Rapkine, Louis
Rapkine, Sarah
Rappleye, Willard C.
Rapport, Maurice M.
Rasmussen, Howard
Ratner, Sarah
Raven, Charles E.
Rawson, Rulon W.
Raymo, Robert R.
Redlich, Frederick C.
Reeck, Gerald R.
Reed, Donald E.
Reeds, Karen
Rees, Douglas
Reese, Colin B.
Regna, Peter
Reich, Edward
Reichardt, Konstantin
Reingold, Nathan
Ressler, Charlotte
Reyes, Vincent P.
Rich, Alexander
Rich, Daniel H.
Richards, Alfred N.
Richards, Frederic M.
Richman, Paul G.
Rickert, William S.
Rieder, Sidney V.
Riesen, Willis H.
Riggs, Douglas S.
Rimington, Claude
Rinsler, M.G.
Ripley, S. Dillon
Rittenberg, David
Robbins, Kenneth C.
Robbins, Phillips W.
Roberts, Sidney
Robin, Eugene D.
Robinson, Frank Arnold
Robinson, Gloria
Robinson, Joseph D.
Roblin, Richard O.
Rocchi, Raniero
Roche, Jean
Rocke, Alan J.
Rockefeller Foundation
Rockefeller Institute
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Univ. Archives
Rockefeller Univ. Press
Roe, Joseph H.
Rogers, Gary A.
Roh, J.K.
Roman, W.
Roos, Albert
Rose, Irwin A.
Rose, William C.
Roseman, Saul
Rosenbaum, Joel
Rosenberg, Leon E.
Rosenberg, Miriam
Rossi-Fanelli, Allesandro
Rossiter, Margaret W.
Rostow, Eugene V.
Rothschild, Victor
Roughton, Francis J.W.
Rous, Peyton
Rubey, William W.
Rubin, Lewis P.
Ruddle, Frank H.
Rudinger, Josef
Russell, John M.
Ruttenberg, Michael
Ryan, Dennis
Ryan, Francis J.
Rychlik, Ivan
Ryle, Andrew P.
Sabin, Albert B.
Sachdev, Goverdhan P.
Sakakibara, Shumpei
Salengo, John
Salk, Jonas E.
Salomon, Kurt
Salter, Eleanor
Samuel, David
Sampath-Kumar, P.S.
Sanger, Frederick
Sano, Seiyo
Sarma, Padubidri S.
Sarotte, Mary E.
Saskin, Edward
Saunders, Bernard C.
Sawyer, John E.
Sayer, Jane M.